Make a Mario style side scroller, but with an Indian auntie as the protagonist.
In an Indian building and her main attack is to throw chappals.
Chappals.
Use sprites from the internet.
So okay, we've got the output.
Auntie's revenge.
These bratty kids are making noise in the corridor.
Use arrow keys to jump and move.
Press Z to throw chappals.
There's no output.
Dude, there is no output.
Where is the auntie or the building?
Where is the output?
There's no output.
I talk to Gemini like this.
I'm just like, dude, there's no output.
I literally type the word dude.
Dude, there's no output.
Where is the auntie or the building?
So we now have the auntie.
She looks angry.
There's an emoji on her head actually.
It's created a nice little sigh for me.
I'm just gonna throw chappals at these stupid kids.
How dare they sit in my building?
Simply sitting and scrolling.
Not even subscribing to Varun Maya.
Nobody would really play a game like this.
I think these are very, very simple, small things.
But I think it's useful for marketing.
Like if you're a brand and you have a cool idea around marketing,
something, some product that you're launching,
you should be making simple games like this.
We are now entering that world where we used to have
mini-clip games many, many years ago.
You can now do that as a brand for a marketing launch,
which I think is pretty cool.
You should take advantage of it.